<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AR-Foods</string>
    <string name="arlanguage">العربية</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="enlangauge">English</string>
    <string name="alexsusageintegr">2 onions medium\n
2 tomatoes\n
2 turkey pepper\n
5 Green Pepper Peeled Green\n
0.5 kg sausage</string>
    <string name="alexsusagway">1 - bring a bowl and put a little oil after, cut the sausage to the rings and heat it well.\n

2 - After extracting the sausage from the oil, leave it in a side dish then leave the oil as it is.\n
3 - Put the onion cubes, tomatoes and green peppers in the oil until they take the golden color, and spoon them two tablespoons of tomato paste and set them on fire for 5 minutes.\n

4 - Guest cut the sausage to the tomato and put the salt and black pepper and my heart well\n
5. Scandinavian sausage is served hot with municipal bread or vinot and tahini salad, and can be served with white rice.</string>
    <string name="beanwitheggway">Place the beans in the pan on the low heat, and then raise it until it becomes a rather thick mixture.\n
        Add salt, lemon juice, chili pepper and a little water, then stir until ingredients are mixed together.\n
        Add the olive oil to the beans, and let it warm a little with the beans.\n
        Place the eggs in a side bowl, add salt and a little black pepper, skim the fork well, then pour it over the beans with a good stirring until the eggs are cooked well.\n
        Cover the pan for three minutes until the eggs are fully maturing.\n
        Serve the beans with hot scrambled eggs with fresh local bread, some of your family's favorite antipasti,
        decorate the dish with finely chopped parsley, and a few finely chopped green onions, all of which can be changed
        - according to family taste.</string>
    <string name="beanwithegginteg">.250 grams of boiled beans\n
. Half a teaspoon of salt\n
. A pinch of lemon salt\n
. A pinch of red pepper\n
. olive oil\n
. Four eggs.</string>
    <string name="chickenrollinteg">Half a kilo of chopped chicken
 2 tbsp
 an egg \n
  Powder of garlic powder onion\n
  Ginger powder lemon juice\n
  Salt black pepper\n
  Water for saliva\n
Pepper black olive colors\n
 Chopped parsley</string>
    <string name="chickenrollway">Mix ingredients together\n
* Individual components on aluminum foil in square and individual form with padding, and cover and cover well with aluminum foil\n
* Roll the roll in the boiling water on the fire\n
* Leave the roller to cool and then cut and feet\n
* It can be preserved before cutting</string>
    <string name="molokhiinteg">1 kg Molokhia leaves, green well washed and filtered\n
6 garlic cloves, minced or finely chopped\n
2 tbsp coriander, dry\n
1 tablespoon margarine, or 2 tablespoons corn oil as desired\n
4 cup chicken broth, or broth, as desired\n
2 tbsp corn oil, as desired</string>
    <string name="molokhiway">We prepare the meloukia after drying and we cut or cut it with a lathe until it is very soft, or even the kernels are poured until smooth.\n
Put the sauce on any amount of fire and add the soup any broth until heated a little,
        and then add the Mallokhia to the soup and turn them well to homogenize together.\n
When the mulukhya starts to boil a little, prepare a pan of any frying pan and put the ghee,
        garlic and coriander, and put them on fire and heat them together until the color of the dish is tilted to the golden.\n
        Then add them to the melokhia and turn quickly and then put out the fire.</string>
    <string name="koshriinteg">A cup of lentils with a meal\n
A cup of rice\n
A cup of noodles\n
A large onion cut into small cubes\n
Spoon of oil\n
Spoon of salt</string>
    <string name="koshriway">1. Prepare a pot and place the onions in plenty of oil until you get the golden color.\n
2 - separate the onions from the oil, and put on a clean napkin to be purified of oil.\n
3 - in the rest of the oil in the pot, national put noodles until you take the gold color.\n
4 - guests of the white time to the noodles and continued to flipping with salt and cumin.\n
5 - National lentil soaked for 10 minutes before starting the previous steps, then collect a liter of water for 20 minutes, and make sure of the near maturity.\n
6 - Guest lentils to rice and noodles and put as much water as appropriate and leave them on low heat.\n
7 - Wait until you confirm the maturity of the kushary completely.</string>
    <string name="kosabashamelinteg">800 grams of chopped rings\n
200 g chopped onions\n
5 g garlic minced\n
20 gm green mint\n
50 g butter\n\n

Beshlam\n
Lethalben\n
1 bag full of Knorr\n
100 grams Rami cheese spread\n

Fillers\n
Minced meat\n
400 g of chopped onions\n
100 g of oil\n
30 gm beef seasonings from Knorr\n
Black pepper to taste\n
100g Sausage Knorr\n
Salt and Pepper</string>
    <string name="kosabashamelway">1 - Put a liter of milk in a pot on the fire to boiling and add a bag of Bashmol of Knorr and leave on a quiet fire for two minutes and leave to cool

To work the minced meat\n
2 - Baihh onion and add the onion and stir well Add the chopped meat and stir well and dipped hanging sauce Knorr and meat seasonings of Knorr, salt and pepper and stir well for 10 minutes to maturity

"To cook the sauce properly\n
3 - Put the clove cut rings in a bowl of beef, onions and garlic and spin well and add mint and cinnamon, salt and pepper and fluctuation only half only and put in a refinery to get out of excess water\n
4 - then put in a bowl of chopped meat with a spoon and a little of the Bashmil\n
5 - We bring the tajn and paint a little bit of the liver and then Balashmal
The mixture is covered with balsamic and Roman cheese spread on the face and enters the oven until maturity and reaches the color of gold and hot</string>
    <string name="torlimeatinteg">Kilo and half cubed meat\n
200 grams of chopped onions\n
200 g Cubic Islands\n
200 grams of potato cubes\n
200 grams of cube cubes\n
200 grams green beans\n
200 grams of green fruit\n
800 grams of Canorr sauce\n
100 g butter\n
4 cubes of tender meat from Knorr\n
100 g of oil\n
salt and pepper as needed</string>
    <string name="torlimeatway">1 - seasoning the herring salt and pepper in a bowl with a little of the butter and leave aside\n
2 - Put the oil and add the onion and stir well until it drips and add a sauce Knor on fire to boiling\n
3 - Add all vegetables and cubes of meat broth from Knorr and cubes of fresh meat until boiling for 5 minutes\n
4 - then placed in a casserole and covered with aluminum for 30 minutes\n
5 - Lift the aluminum until it takes a golden wok and made hot with rice</string>
    <string name="gmbrehameinteg">Half a kilogram of shrimps, cleanser and pans (2 cups)\n
2 onion, sliced\n
2 tomatoes, peeled and cut into thin slices\n
Spoon of Knorr Chicken Spoon Powder\n
Half a teaspoon of salt\n
Half a teaspoon of black pepper\n
3 chili pepper, circles clip
Half a cup of oil\n
Half a teaspoon of sugar</string>
    <string name="gmbrehameway">- Rinse the shrimp and clean.\n
- Fry onions in oil and stir until golden color.\n
- Cook the tomatoes and stir, add the salt, and powder canor chicken powder, black pepper and chili.\n
- Leaves on fire until thickened and darker. Add the shrimp and stir, add sugar and boil for 30 minutes until thickened. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="bsarainteg">Kilo of peeled beans\n
200 grams of dry Mallochia.\n
5 g garlic minced\n
100 g olive oil\n
4 grated vegetable cube of Knorr\n
5 grams of cumin.\n
50 g of parsley finely chopped.\n
20 g of coriander leaves.\n
200 g of onion clip.\n
200 g of water</string>
    <string name="besaraway">1 - Wash the beans well and soak in water for two hours and then put in a bowl with water and cubes of broth vegetables from Knorr on fire and is completed\n
2 - Grind in an electric mixer with a little water as needed (to keep the mixture somewhat strong), and then add to the Mallochia, and continue cooking until all mature.\n
3 - Heat the oil in a pot on fire and fry the garlic, onions and coriander, and sprinkle with salt and cumin and then add to the mix of beans.
Serve hot</string>
    <string name="khrshofinteg">1/2 kilo of boiled artichoke\n
2 cups fresh spinach\n
1 onion large size, sliced ​​slice\n
2 garlic cloves minced\n
1/2 teaspoon lemon juice\n
1 Cinnamon Vegetable Soup Cube\n
1/2 tablespoon flour\n
2 tbsp butter\n
1/4 cup cooked cream\n
1 cup milk\n
1/2 cup of grated mozzarella cheese\n
1 teaspoon black pepper\n
Salt, to taste</string>
    <string name="khrshofway">Artichoke pieces are boiled into halves and kept aside.\n
· In a frying pan, melt a tablespoon of butter and sauté the onion for a few minutes. \n
        Add the spinach and lemon juice and stir with the onions on medium heat until the spinach melts. Saves by.\n
In a saucepan, melt a spoon of butter and stir with flour and garlic until the mixture is yolk.\n
        Then add the Canor vegetable cumin cube with milk and whisk until the mixture thickens slightly.\n
Add the cream and season the mixture with salt and black pepper.\n
In an oven tray, ground artichoke and spinach mixture, pour the mixture over it and cover with mozzarella cheese.\n
Bake in the oven for 20 minutes until golden.
Hot offer.</string>
    <string name="negrscointeg">Kilo and a half macaroni bar or spaghetti\n
One and a half kilos of chicks and a piece of very high or chopped\n
400 g of chopped onions\n
20 g garlic minced\n
100 g mushrooms\n
6 Cannor Chicken Soup Cube\n
200 grams of oil and oil\n
5 grams nutmeg\n


Beshlam\n\n
Liter milk\n
Bag by Shamal Knorr\n
500 grams Parmesan cheese spread or Romani</string>
    <string name="negrscoway">Bechamel\n
1 - Put the milk in the pot on fire to boiling and add a bag of Bashmal Knor and turn on the fire for a quiet 4 minutes and leave aside to cool

Chicks\n
2 - Taste on the fire add the onion and onion and garlic stir well Add the mushrooms and stir and add the chicks and stir and broth Chicken Knorr and turn everyone on a quiet fire for 5 minutes and leave aside.
To roast macaroni\n
1 - water on the fire boil add salt add noodles Climb 3/4 only and well filtered
</string>
    <string name="chickenballinteg">Kilo and half chicken breasts, minced\n
Gram Spices of Knorr\n
5 eggs beaten and seasoned with salt and pepper\n
10 grams Picking Powder\n
150 grams of toast\n
5 g white pepper\n
As desired by salt\n
5 grams paprika\n
10 slices of toast, fresh and finely chopped\n
50 g egg whites\n
5 g garlic, mashed</string>
    <string name="chickenballway">1 - Mix chicken with eggs, chopped bread crumbs, pepper, salt and paprika seasoning chicks of Knorr and garlic well until the paste\n
2. Prepare small balls of medium size mix\n
3 - Dip the balls in egg white and then in the chopped bread\n
4 - Reduce balls in hot oil until it becomes golden and then hot</string>
    <string name="babaganoginteg">2 large eggplant\n
1/2 finely ground sweet red pepper\n
2 cloves of crushed garlic\n
1/4 finely chopped hot pepper\n
2 lemon juice\n
1/4 cup water\n
1/4 cup tahini\n
2 tbsp olive oil\n
1 tbsp salt</string>
    <string name="babaganougway">Wash the eggplant and deep holes in the knife with eggplant from the outside to the inside, grind the eggplant until fully cooked and become very tender.\n
Remove the eggplant from the black crust and set aside, prepare the sauce with food, place the tahini, lemon juice, olive oil, salt and water and mix well.\n
Add the garlic, sweet and hot turkey and mix well. Add the grilled pudding and mix until the mixture is mixed.</string>
    <string name="floursaladinteg">Text of a cup of flour\n
2 cloves of garlic\n
salt\n\n
Hot sauce\n
3 tablespoons vinegar\n
Lemon juice\n
3 tablespoons of yogurt\n
A cup and a watercolor</string>
    <string name="floursaladway">Put the flour in a plate of gouit, boil the water and then fast quickly and it is bigly on the tahini and my heart with a fork quickly, as far as the fish to the sweetness, he gave them garlic, mashed, yogurt,
        vinegar and the optimal salt and chop according to your taste</string>
    <string name="potatosaladinteg">Half a kilo of small peeled potatoes\n
A cup of milk\n
Half a cup of sesame paste\n
Two lemons\n
2 cloves of garlic\n
Half cup of water\n
Teaspoon salt</string>
    <string name="potatosaladway">Put the potatoes in salted water, then cut them. \n
        Put the potatoes with the rest of the ingredients in the electric mixer until they are crushed.\n
        Put the mambal in the refrigerator for 10 minutes and then put them on.</string>
    <string name="hmoussaladinteg">2 cups chickpeas\n
400 g cucumber cubes section\n
400 grams of cherry tomatoes chopped half\n
Medium onion chopped or sliced ​​as desired\n
Green peppers cut\n
300 g mozzarella cheese cubes\n
A cup of freshly sliced ​​basil leaves\n\n
    ingredients of sauce:
2 teaspoons balsamic vinegar\n
2 teaspoons honey\n
2 tablespoons olive oil\n
Tablespoon lemon juice\n
Salt and Pepper</string>
    <string name="homussaladway">Stir chickpeas until tender and may take an average of 15 minutes\n
- In a deep bowl mix the chopped vegetables with chickpeas and cheese\n
- Mix the ingredients of the sauce together in a small bowl and cook well\n
- Add the sauce to the Authority before it is presented immediately and their hearts well</string>
    <string name="collslosaladinteg">Cubans of green or red cabbage are finely chopped\n
. Two large islands, where they are peeled and sprayed smoothly\n
. Six tablespoons of regular mayonnaise, can be increased as desired\n
. Six tablespoons of coarse white sugar. A glass of yogurt\n
. 2 teaspoons salt, or more as desired\n
. A teaspoon of black pepper\n
. Tablespoon of white vinegar or apple vinegar, and if vinegar is not available, lemon juice can be used.
</string>
    <string name="coolsloway">It is preferable to use a food processor to crush the cabbage,
        but if it is not available, be careful to cut it very gently.\n
        Add the carrots to the soft cabbage,
        mix well with it.\n
        Add the amount of sugar to the mixture of vegetables, and move well until the sugar mixed with cabbage and carrots,
        where it will notice the exit of water from vegetables as a result of sugar.\n
        Move the vegetables to the strainer,
        and leave them for at least an hour, to make sure the vegetables are filtered out of the entire water.\n
        Move the vegetables to a deep, well-sized bowl.\n
        Mix mayonnaise, yogurt, salt and pepper in addition to vinegar,
        in a suitable bowl.\n
        Pour the Mayonnaise mixture into the vegetables and stir well,
        until all the ingredients are mixed together.\n
        Cover the container with nylon and place in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes before use.
</string>
    <string name="taboulasaladinteg">2 parsley bunch, finely chopped\n
1/4 mint bouillon, finely chopped\n
4 tomatoes, large size chopped\n
1 medium onion, finely chopped\n
3 tablespoons soft, washed broccoli\n
Juice 2 sour lemon\n\n
Two tablespoons of pomegranate molasses
   1 cup of olive oil\n
1/4 teaspoon soft cinnamon\n
Pour according to desire\n
Salt, to taste</string>
    <string name="taboulasaladway">
        - Soak the bulgur in sour juice and leave on the side, rub the chopped onion with diced garlic and soft cinnamon then leave on the side.\n

- In a deep bowl add both parsley, mint, tomato, onion, and bulgur and mix the ingredients of the salad.\n

Add the pomegranate and salt, then mix the tiboule and salt to taste, adding the acid juice as desired.\n

- Add olive oil to the tabbouleh and offer immediately.\n

Serve with lettuce leaves and cabbage.
    </string>
    <string name="piesaladinteg">Large grain of eggplant\n
. Two large potatoes\n
. A bead of sweet green peppers\n
. Two pieces of squash\n
. Five leaves of lettuce\n
. A cup of boiled chickpeas\n
. Teaspoon of cumin\n
. A quarter cup of finely chopped parsley\n
. A large loaf of plain bread\n
. Four tablespoons of lemon juice\n
. Vegetable oil (corn oil, sunflower oil) is abundant for frying\n
. Salt, to taste. Tahini sauce.\n\n
    Ingredients of tahini sauce:\n
  Half a cup of tahini\n
. Four cloves of garlic, mashed\n
. A glass of yogurt\n
. Two tablespoons of vinegar</string>
    <string name="piesaladway">Preparation of tahini sauce:\n
 We put in a deep bowl all of the tahini, yogurt, garlic, vinegar\n
. Beat the ingredients using a manual handkerchief for 2 minutes, leaving the pot aside until it is needed\n
. Preparation of pans salad:\n
 Wash both zucchini, eggplant, potatoes, sweet green peppers, lettuce leaves, and peel both eggplant and potatoes.\n
        Cut eggplant,
        potatoes, squash, bread into small cubes, and cut lettuce and sweet green peppers into longitudinal strips.\n
        Sprinkle the eggplant cubes with a little salt and leave them for 15 minutes to get rid of the bitter taste in it,
        then wash it and half the well.\n
        Sprinkle the vegetable oil in a deep skillet and place on high heat for a few minutes until the oil is well heated.\n
        Take the potatoes, and then the bread, zucchini and eggplant, respectively, and each time we take out some vegetable oil and put it on drying paper to get rid of the oil stuck to it.\n
        Add eggplant, bread, zucchini, potatoes, chickpeas, lemon juice, lettuce, parsley, sweet green peppers,
        cumin, salt and stir them together with a tablespoon.\n
        Pour the tahini sauce over the bowl containing the pans.\n
        Put the salad in a serving dish, sprinkle the dish with lemon slices, and parsley sticks.</string>
    <string name="sezarsaladinteg">2 chicken breast cubes section\n
1 brown spaghetti baguette (Penne boiled)\n
1 cup mayonnaise 1/3 cup sour cream\n
1 clove of crushed garlic\n
1 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce\n
1 small lettuce head, washed and finely sliced 1 1/2 cup cherry tomatoes cut in half\n
4 green onions, sliced 1/2 cups sliced Parmesan cheese\n
1/2 cup toast toast bread cubes and toasted\n
1 tbsp olive oil, salt and pepper as desired</string>
    <string name="sezarsaladway">To prepare the salad: In a bowl, mix the mayonnaise with sour cream, Worcester sauce, garlic and black pepper.\n
2 - add noodles on the spice and stir to mix the pasta pasta with spices\n
3-Enter the pasta noodle mix for 30 minutes\n
4 - In the frying pan on the fire we protect the olive oil and add the chicken and season with salt and pepper\n
5 - stir the chicken on the fire to simmer and brown from all sides for 7 minutes and then raise the chicken from the frying pan\n
6. In a bowl, mix the mixed pasta with the lettuce, tomatoes, green onions and chicken\n
7 - Add the toast and stir to mix all the ingredients together\n
8. Add the cheese and stir well\n
9 - Progress and health and wellness</string>
    <string name="egglphantinteg">
        Medium eggplant egg\n
Oil for the minority\n
garlic\n
Salt, to taste\n
Lemons\n
Green Pepper\n
Red pepper\n
latency
    </string>
    <string name="egglphantway">
        - Cut the eggplant either circles or cubes as desired\n
- We get a little salt and let it get rid of excess water\n
- Wash it and then pour it in the oil and remove it on dry paper to remove the excess oil\n
- We prepare the seasoning by cutting the pepper and garlic and put them in the cup with cumin and salt\n
- Operate the cup until Nfrm ingredients we get out of the cup and squeeze the lemon\n
- Seasoned eggplant mix and served with different dishes
    </string>
    <string name="watercressinteg">
        Two packs of watercress\n
. Two medium sized tomatoes\n
. A small slice of onion\n
. Two slices of option\n
. Half a cup of walnuts\n
. half cup of olive oil\n
. Three tablespoons of white vinegar\n
. Three tablespoons of lemon juice\n
. Tablespoon of pomegranate molasses\n
. Half a teaspoon of salt\n
. quarter tea spoon of black Peper\n
. Half teaspoon of sumac. Half a teaspoon of chop.
    </string>
    <string name="watercressway">
        Wash the watercress, and with a towel moistened with water and put it in the refrigerator until he recovers his glasses.\n
        Place the watercress in the serving dish.\n
        Place onion slices, tomatoes and cucumber over watercress.\n
        The nut is placed above this mixture.\n
        To prepare the salad mix, put the oil, lemon juice, pomegranate, white vinegar, salt, salt, and sumac in Bartman, and let it cool until the mixture is ready.\n
        As well as the representatives of the Authority.

    </string>
    <string name="pastatunainteg">Five hundred grams of pasta, preferably from good pasta.\n
  A full-size tuna tray.\n
  Medium onion.\n
  Three grains of tomatoes.\n
  Colorful turkey pepper.\n
        A clove of garlic. Two cups of sweet corn. Half a cup of black olives
. Four tablespoons of mayonnaise.\n
        A tablespoon of ketchup. \n
        A teaspoon of recovered sauce\n
. A glass of yogurt.\n
        A pinch of salt.\n
        A pinch of black pepper.</string>
    <string name="pastatunaway">
        Cook the pasta with a pot filled with water on the fire, add a little salt and oil. When the water boils well, add the pasta, and wait until it is well cooked.\n
        Sprinkle the peppers for 10 minutes, and their hearts on all sides. When they are well cooked, cut them into thin slices.\n
        Cut the onion into slices, and the tomatoes into cubes.\n
        Stir well boiled pasta, then mix tomatoes, onions and pepper with pasta, add corn and olives, and mix.\n
        Bring the tuna box, well-oiled, and then add to the previous mixture, and gently cauliflower.\n
        Cut the garlic, stir in the oil on the fire in a pan, and then bring a bowl, and my heart with ketchup, yogurt, mayonnaise and garlic as well.\n
        Add the whole ingredients to each other, and put the appropriate salt and black pepper. \n
        Put the mixture in the refrigerator for some time.\n
        Put it in the serving dish, and give it to your family.\n
        You can add parsley or basil on the face; to decorate the dish,
        give it a delicious flavor.
    </string>
    <string name="tunabtatasinteg">
        * Tuna (2 pack).\n
* Olives cut and uncooked (1/2 cup).\n
* Potatoes cut into cubes and fried (3 tablets).\n
* Parsley ( bouquet).\n
* Coriander ( bouquet).\n
* One onion cut into wings.\n
* One pack of filtered onions (preferably fresh onions).\n
* Stuffed or boiled mushroom.\n
* Mayonnaise (cup).\n
* Chopped (2 tbsp).\n
* 1 large tomatoes cut.\n
* black pepper.\n
* Salt, to taste).
    </string>
    <string name="tunabtatsway">
        1. Rub onion with vinegar and salt in a side bowl.\n
2. Filter the tuna from the oil.\n
3. Melt the tuna well in a deep bowl.\n
4. Add the onion, chopped with vinegar, salt and all the ingredients to the tuna except for the tomatoes.\n
5. My heart plug well.\n
6. Add salt as desired.\n
7. Place the dish in the refrigerator until the date of submission.\n
8. Zinni dish with tomato jujug at presentation.\n
9. My feet are cool.
    </string>
    <string name="greenoninonsoupinte">
        1 cup yellow lentils, washed and drained\n
1 cup chickpeas, washed and drained\n
1  liters of water\n
1 Islands, peeled and cut into cubes\n
2 tbsp fresh ginger, peeled and chopped\n
2 tbsp Curry, Madras, you can use more hot types\n
2 tbsp olive oil, or butter\n
6 green onions, leeks, thin slices do not get rid of the green part
 cup small raisins\n
 cup tomato sauce\n
1 pack of almond milk\n
Salt to taste\n
1 bunch coriander, finely chopped
    </string>
    <string name="greenonionsoupway">
        Add hummus, lentils and the amount of ginger with carrots in the amount of water in a covered pot until the chickpeas are cooked.\n
Meanwhile, roast the curry powder over the fire until it smelled. Then lift it directly from the fire so as not to burn.\n
Heat the oil or butter in a skillet. Add three quarters of the onion with the remaining ginger, raisins and hearts on the fire for 2 minutes, add the tomato sauce and continue stirring for 2 minutes.\n
Add the roasted curry to the onion mixture and my heart well.\n
Add the onion mixture to the soup with salt and almond milk.\n
Leave the pot without cover for 20 minutes or more depending on the preferred texture of the soup, increasing its density as cooking continues.
Garnish with coriander and green onions
    </string>
    <string name="shofansoupinteg">
        1/2 white rice\n
2 chicken breast\n
1/4 oatmeal\n
5 Water\n
Salt and black pepper to taste\n
3 Clove Love\n
1 lemon citric acid
    </string>
    <string name="shofansoupway">
        1 - Cut the chicken breast into small cubes, put it in a pot of fire with two cups of water and when boiling, add the beads of cloves
And let him boil a little.\n
2. When the chicken is cooked, cut the onion and add it with the chicken, add the salt as desired.\n
3 - Wash and spread rice for 5 minutes and then add to the chicken with the rest of the water, cover the pot until it is cooked and after 10 minutes I lay
Fire, and mix it with the handbrake quickly until all the ingredients are homogenized.\n
4 - restore the pot on fire, if thick or thick mixture you can add water to ease it then add oats, parsley and lemon and the rest
Ingredients and leave on fire until cooked ..
    </string>
    <string name="ryhansoupinteg">
        1 medium cabbage \n
1 tbsp minced basil \n
4 tomatoes\n
2 hot green peppers\n
6 onions, preferably green onions\n
6 medium garlic cloves\n
2 tbsp tomato juice\n
2 cube chicken broth\n
Chopsticks according to desire\n
1/4 teaspoon salt
    </string>
    <string name="ryhansoupway">
        1. Bring all the ingredients in the water until they are well cooked, then leave them to cool.\n
2. Put the boiled vegetables in the electric mixer and stir well.\n
3. Place the mashed vegetables in a saucepan and add the chicken broth as desired. Leave the soup on the fire to boil for 10 minutes.
minutes.
    </string>
    <string name="lsanasforinteg">
        1/2 cup spaghetti Spaghetti boiled \n
1 cup onions, small cubes \n
4 garlic cloves minced \n
1/2 cup zucchini cubes section \n
1/2 cup grilled eggplant
1/4 cup freshly sliced mushrooms
1/4 cup chopped parsley
1 cup colored peppers cut into cubes
1 tsp olive oil
1 teaspoon chopped hot pepper
Salt and black pepper
1/4 cup soy sauce
    </string>
    <string name="lsanasforway">
        1 - Add the oil and add the onion, garlic, pepper protector, mushrooms, pepper colors and zucchini in a non - stick hot pan and then
Mix a bit. \n
2 - Add eggplant, soy sauce, salt, pepper, leave boiling, add the tongue of the boiled bird, add the parsley and its heart
Then put it hot on your table.

    </string>
    <string name="GarlicSoupinteg">
        5 cloves of crushed garlic\n
1 tbsp tomato sauce\n
1 cube chicken broth\n
Salt and pepper\n
2 1/2 cup water
    </string>
    <string name="garlicsoupway">
        1. In a pot of fire, put the water and leave it until it boils.\n
2. Add the gravy cube and add the garlic, salt and spices.\n
3. When garlic smells, add the sauce and leave it slightly on the fire and feet.\n
    </string>
    <string name="basbousaeshtainteg">
        A glass of sugar.\n
A cup of semolina.\n
  A cup of flour.\n
  A cup of yoghurt.\n
A glass of oil.\n
  A glass of warm water.\n
  A cup of coconut.\n Ingredients of cream:\n
  Three cups of milk.\n
  Four tablespoons of starch.\n
  Sugar according to desire.
    </string>
    <string name="basbosaeshtaway">
        Mix the ingredients of the cream in a saucepan.\n
  We move the ingredients to homogenize and weigh together.\n
  Remove the pot from the fire, then add the water.\n
  Mix the ingredients of the onion.\n
  Add the Pyrex tray with oil.\n
  We put half of the ingredients in Chinese.\n
Put the cream, then the other half of the pepsosa.\n
  Place the Pyrex tray in the oven at 180 ° C for about one hour until it turns brown from the top.\n
  We leave the Chinese so cool, then adorn.\n

    </string>
    <string name="bsbosabl2shtainteg">
A glass of sugar.\n
  A cup of semolina.\n
  A cup of flour.\n
A cup of yoghurt.\n
A glass of oil.\n
A glass of warm water.\n
  A cup of coconut\n\n
        Ingredients of cream:\n
  Three cups of milk.\n
  Four tablespoons of starch.\n
  Sugar according to desire
    </string>
    <string name="bsbosabl2shtaway">
        Mix the ingredients of the cream in a saucepan.\n
  We move the ingredients to homogenize and weigh together.\n
  Remove the pot from the fire, then add the water.\n
  Mix the ingredients of the onion.\n
Add the Pyrex tray with oil.\n
  We put half of the ingredients in Chinese.\n
  Put the cream, then the other half of the pepsosa.\n
Place the Pyrex tray in the oven at 180 ° C for about one hour until it turns brown from the top.\n
  We leave the Chinese so cool, then adorn.
    </string>
    <string name="ricemilkinteg">
        Two cups of rice.\n
Four liters of milk.\n
  Four cups of sugar.
    </string>
    <string name="ricemilkway">
        Put the milk in a saucepan. Wait until the milk boils.\n
  Wash rice, and drain well of water. Add the rice to the milk, then add the sugar.\n
  Wait until the mixture becomes thick.\n
  Remove the pot from the fire. Pour the rice in milk in suitable dishes. Garnish face with cinnamon and coconut.
    </string>
    <string name="blozamhlbeainteg">
        Four glasses of orange juice.\n
  Two cups of sugar.\n
  Eight spoons of starch.\n
  Two tablespoons of cast water. Kg of milk.

    </string>
    <string name="blozaway">
        Place orange juice with a starch spoon in a saucepan on the fire.\n
        We move the components so that they are in harmony with each other. \n
        Add a glass of sugar, a teaspoon of cast water, and move the mixture until it is firm.\n
        Pour the layer of foam into the cups. Put the milk and starch in a pot on the fire. \n
        Add the sugar, move the ingredients until they hold together, then add the water. Pour the mixture over the eggs.\n
        Put the ornaments in the fridge.

    </string>
    <string name="bsbosaoreinteg">
        Four eggs.\n
  Cup only a quarter of sugar.\n
  Cup only a quarter of the oil. A little flannel.\n
  A cup of semolina. A teaspoon of baking powder.\n
  Five beads of hand-broken tea biscuits. Eight beads of hand-broken Oreo.\n
  Small packet of Pakistani vermicelli. Local and condensed milk for watering and decoration.
    </string>
    <string name="bsbosaoreoway">
        Beat eggs, then add sugar.\n
        Mix the sugar with the milk well, then add the flannel and oil, and finally add the semolina and baking powder.\n
        Add the crushed biscuits and Oreo to the basbous mixture. Add the cake tray with flour or oil.\n
        Pour the mixture into Chinese.\n
        Break the noodles and put them on the face. \n
        Place the Chinese in the oven for thirty minutes at a temperature of 180 ° C until it turns red. We take the Chinese out of the oven and pour the local milk directly.

    </string>
    <string name="kbsal7mainteg">
        1 kg lamb
 2 white onion, cut strips
 1 grain balls, finely chopped
 5 tablespoons butter\n
 Salt, to taste
 1 cup tomato sauce
 2 hot green peppers\n
 1 Cinnamon sticks
 3 cloves of cloves
 1 tablespoon paprika, a chimney
 8 Hull Beans\n
 1 Lome
1/2 teaspoon turmeric
 Saffron Brush
 1/2 teaspoon black pepper, ground
 1 cup orange juice\n
1/2 human orange peel
 2 cups US rice, drenched in lukewarm water for 30 minutes and drained\n
 8 cups meat broth
 5 cloves of garlic, crushed\n
  cup nuts, pine nuts, cashew and toaster for decoration
Dough sauce Ingredients: 1 tomato, peeled
 1 hot green pepper\n
1/4 cup green coriander, minced
 2 cloves of garlic\n
 1 lemon juice, juice
 Salt, to taste
    </string>
    <string name="kbsaway">
        Heat the butter in a large saucepan until it becomes light brown.\n
        Add the meat and brown well. \n
        Add the onions. Shallots and fry until they become almost 5 light golden for 5 minutes. Add salt, garlic, green peppers and spices.\n
Add the tomato sauce, saffron and orange juice and stir for 2 minutes, then add the broth of boiled meat and leave on fire for an hour and a half until the meat is cooked Add the orange spray Add the rice and leave on fire for 15 minutes or until it is cooked.\n
Make an aluminum foil and put it in the middle of the rice. Place a piece of burning charcoal in the middle of the boat with a small piece of butter to make smoke with a lid for only 2 minutes.\n
Pour the rice into the serving plate and the meat on the face and decorate with nuts and serve.
    </string>
    <string name="yellowriceinteg">
        3 cups basmati rice\n
4 cups and a half of water boiled chicken\n
1 teaspoon "teaspoon" salt\n
1 teaspoon "teaspoon" cinnamon\n
1 teaspoon "tea spoon" Paprika\n
1 teaspoon "tsp" spices\n
1 tsp "tsp" Optional "chop"\n
Half teaspoon "teaspoon" ground black pepper\n\n
        Chicken mixture:
1 kilo chicken\n
One quarter cup of rose water\n
1 large onion onion quarters\n
2 cloves garlic mashed\n
3 lobes love "Hill"\n
3 Laurel paper\n
2 cinnamon sticks\n
2 tsp "teaspoon" salt\n
1 teaspoon teaspoon saffron\n
1 teaspoon "teaspoon" chopped ginger\n
1 teaspoon "tsp" turmeric
    </string>
    <string name="yellowriceway">
        Wash the chicken with plenty of water, and leave it in an aside.\n
In a small cup, mix the saffron and rose water, and stir them for 5 minutes.\n
Put the saffron mixture over the chicken, and place it on the inside and outside.\n
In a large pot and on high heat, put a large amount of water and chicken, add onions, garlic, bay leaves, cinnamon, lettuce, ginger and turmeric, and leave on fire for an hour until the chicken is cooked.\n
Remove the chicken from the soup, place it in a tray aside, and then half the soup.\n
We start to prepare the rice. We wash the rice well, soak it for half an hour, then drain it from the water.\n
In a large bowl and on high heat, put the soup until it boils.\n
Put the rice in the bowl, add salt, black pepper, cinnamon, spices, paprika and saffron, and stir well until it starts to boil.\n
Cover the rice bowl, then heat the fire, and leave for 40 minutes until cooked.\n
At that time, put the chicken in a tray and place in a preheated oven until red.\n
In a large, flat dish, place the rice and spread the chicken over it.\n
We offer yellow rice with hot chicken with hot dukes sauce.

    </string>
    <string name="hotsalsainteg">
        2 tomatoes\n
2 hot pepper\n
1 cup of ground pepper\n
2 cloves of true garlic\n
2 tbsp "tablespoon" olive oil\n
1 tbsp "spoon" tomato sauce\n
1 teaspoon "teaspoon" Chita\n
Semi-lemon juice\n
1 pack of parsley\n
1 pack coriander green\n
A quarter cup of water
salt
    </string>
    <string name="hotsalsaway">
        Wash the tomatoes, chili pepper and turkey pepper, cut them, then put them in the cup or mixer.\n
Add the green coriander, parsley, garlic, tomato sauce, lemon juice, olive oil, water, salt and spice.\n
Pour all ingredients well until smooth and smooth.\n
Put the hot sauce in the dishes, and serve it with a cup or mandi.
    </string>
    <string name="mandychiinteg">
        4 cups basmati rice\n
2 Kilo chicken section\n
2 large onion chopped onion\n
2 green turkey pepper\n
1 large hanging oil\n
1 small saffron hanging\n
2 cinnamon sticks\n
10 chopsticks\n
10 lobes "Hill"\n
10 cloves of black pepper\n
4 Laurel paper\n
salt\n
Spices\n
Water
    </string>
    <string name="mandychicway">
        Wash the chicken well, and cut.\n
Wash the rice well, then soak in water for half an hour.\n
Saffron is placed in a quarter cup of water, left aside.\n
Put the oil in a pot on the fire, add the onion, and stir until it turns brown.\n
Add chicken pieces, one after the other and stir until golden color is gained, then lift aside.\n
Bring the chicken back into the bowl and add cinnamon, cloves, lettuce, bay leaves, black pepper, spices, salt and turkey pepper.\n
Place water until covered, leave on medium heat for 30 minutes until cooked.\n
Remove the chicken from the soup, stir in an oven tray, and place in the grill to brown.\n
Take the amount of 6 cups of soup, and put in a pot on the fire until boiling.\n
Add the rice and saffron mixture, then cover and simmer for 30 minutes until cooked.\n
Place the rice in the dish, and place the chicken pieces over it.\n
Serve hot with yogurt sauce.
    </string>
    <string name="tandorichickeninteg">
        1 medium size chicken\n
A quarter cup of olive oil\n
One quarter cup tomato sauce\n
1 small salt suspended\n
A small hanging quarter of black pepper\n
A small hanging quarter of soft cinnamon\n
A quarter of a small suspended ground clove\n
A quarter of a small suspension is a melted "hill"\n
One quarter of a small garlic powder\n
One quarter small onion powder
    </string>
    <string name="tandorchickenway">
        1 Wash the chicken well, divide long halves.\n
Put the oil in a bowl, add to the sauce, salt, black pepper, cinnamon, cloves, lettuce, garlic powder and onions, mix well.\n
Let the chicken stir well and leave it for a night.\n
  Light the electric grill with oil and place the chicken on it.\n
It fluctuates from time to time until it ripens and is reddened.\n
They are lifted from the grill, made hot.
    </string>
    <string name="shakshokainteg">
        Sold a kilo of chopped chopped meat\n
4 eggs\n
1 onion chopped\n
1 cup of ground pepper\n
Chili pepper "optional"\n
Half a cup of tomato juice\n
2 outstanding large tomato sauce\n
salt\n
black pepper\n
latency\n
oil
    </string>
    <string name="shaksokaway">
        Put the oil in a pan on the fire until it is heated.\n
Add the onion, stir until it wilts and changes its color.\n
Add hot turkeys and stir until they are soaked.\n
Add the chopped meat and stir until the color changes.\n
Add tomato juice and sauce, and stir well.\n
Season with salt, black pepper and cumin, and stir again.\n
The mixture is drilled in the number of eggs, and the eggs are placed in it.\n
Cover, and simmer for 7 minutes until the eggs are cooked.\n
Put in the dish, and served hot with bread and roast.
    </string>
    <string name="romansaladinteg">
        Spinach leaves\n
1 cup vita cheese\n
1 cup Mango clip cubes\n
2 cup pomegranate love\n
2 tablespoons lemon juice
    </string>
    <string name="romansaladway">
        Mix the pomegranate, mango, spinach and feta cheese.\n
Bake lemon juice.\n
Give it to your family.
    </string>
    <string name="flowersaladinteg">
        1 cup boiled cut flower\n
1 bunch of watercress\n
3 tbsp olive oil\n
1/4 tablespoon salt\n
2 tbsp vinegar\n
2 tbsp lemon juice
    </string>
    <string name="flowersaladway">
        Pour broccoli into the oven until fully cooked. In the serving dish, the watercress and then the cauliflower and their hearts together.
Add salt, lemon juice, vinegar, olive oil and my salad heart and then her feet.
    </string>
    <string name="goatsaladinteg">
        Tablespoon olive oil\n
Tablespoon balsamic vinegar\n
Salt spray\n
A glass of watercress\n
2 tbsp goat cheese\n
Toast Asmar\n
nut\n
1/2 cup dried cherries\n
1/2 cup cherry tomatoes\n
Oregano workshop
    </string>
    <string name="goatsaladway">
        1. In the bowl of olive oil, balsamic vinegar, salt, oregano with stirring.\n
2. In a bowl of brown toast.\n
3. Cheese with cheese.\n
4. On the cheese put the walnut and dried cherries.\n
5. In the serving bowl and the watercress, and above it put the cherry tomatoes and then more dried cherries.\n
6. Saski sauce I attended at the beginning.\n
7. Make toast with cheese.\n
8. Distribute the remaining nuts.\n
9. On the face of Origano spray.
    </string>
    <string name="ftoshinteg">
        A cup of lettuce minced\n
1 cup chopped cherry tomatoes\n
Chopped cucumber\n
3 radishes section\n
1/4 cup thyme leaves\n
1/2 red onion cut\n
1/21 tbsp lemon lemon juice\n
2 tbsp olive oil\n
1/2 teaspoon salt\n
Teaspoon thick\n
Sun Bates
    </string>
    <string name="ftoshway">
        In the dish place all the ingredients.\n
Mix until fully homogeneous.\n
Put the salad in the serving bowl.
    </string>
    <string name="msasatinteg">
        1 cup of Capricorn tomatoes\n
1 cup mozzarella balls\n
3 tablespoons olive oil\n
Basil leaves\n
1/4 tablespoon salt\n
1/4 teaspoon pepper\n
2 tablespoons vinegar\n
Wooden chopsticks

    </string>
    <string name="msasatway">
        1 - Bring the leaves of the basil and then put the balls of Caprizi and mozzarella cheese and fix it in wooden sticks.\n
2. Season with salt, pepper, vinegar and olive oil, then place on the serving plate and feet.
    </string>
    <string name="shamndrinteg">
        beet\n
Fresh Cheese\n
Salt spray\n
Bharar sweet soup\n
Balsamic vinegar
    </string>
    <string name="shamndrway">
        1. Place the cheese in a bowl.\n
2. Brush with salt and spices and stir with stirring.\n
3. Cut the beetroot slices.\n
4. In the serving dish, place a beetroot and above it a single layer of cheese.\n
5. Place another layer of beets over the cheese and repeat the above until you have 4 layers of beets and 3 layers of cheese.\n
6. Repeat the above until you finish each quantity that you have.\n
7. Plexiglass vinegar to power before serving.
    </string>
    <string name="khrshofmilksoupinteg">
        Artichoke Cup Clip\n
3 green onion clip\n
3 cups broth\n
1 cup broth\n
1 cup condensed milk\n
1 cup boiled potato pieces\n
2 tablespoons butter\n
1 chopped onion\n
3 garlic cloves minced\n
1/4 tablespoon salt\n
1/4 teaspoon pepper
    </string>
    <string name="khrshofmilksoupway">
        1. Fry onion and garlic in butter until yellowing.\n
2. Add the green onion, artichoke, potatoes, broth, water and pepper and set them on fire until softened.\n
3. Mix with a little electric bat and add gradually condensed milk with mixing.\n
4. Lift it on the fire again and let it heat up and then feet.
    </string>
    <string name="khodartmrinteg">
        1 kilo drew peeled and cut\n
2 bunch of chopped dill\n
4 bunch coriander chopped\n
6 bunch of chopped flour\n
2 finely chopped onion\n
Juice 4 lemon seeds\n
5 beads pass without nuclei\n
olive oil\n
salt\n
Red pepper\n
Turmeric
    </string>
    <string name="khodartmrway">
        In a saucepan, heat the onions in the olive oil until it melts. Add the turnips until the color changes.\n
        Add the vegetables and my heart until you are wet. Add salt, turmeric and red pepper.\n
Add the boiling water to the mixture until the ingredients are submerged and covered with a small amount.\n
Add the dates and lemon mixture and leave on low heat for about half an hour until the mixture is homogeneous.
    </string>
    <string name="ftrcreamyinteg">
        1/21 tablespoon butter\n
2 tbsp vegetable oil\n
A cup of onions\n
Clove garlic\n
200 g fresh mushrooms\n
11 \ 2 tablespoon flour\n
1/2 teaspoon white condiment\n
3 cups of meat broth\n
1/2 teaspoon salt\n
1/2 cup of cooking cream
    </string>
    <string name="ftrcreamyway">
        1. In a pan on the fire, put the butter and oil and stir with stirring.\n
2. Add the onions, stirring until soft.\n
3. Put the garlic and repeat flipping.\n
4. Add mushrooms, flour, white parsley, stirring after each addition.\n
5. Place the meat broth.\n
6. Pour the soup on the fire as it is visible in front of you till the full homogeneity.\n
7. Season the soup with salt, cook and cook with stirring.\n
8. Leave the pot on the fire for 10 minutes.
    </string>
    <string name="sbn5lsaninteg">
        150 g spinach\n
Spaghetti Spaghetti Spaghetti 3/4\n
Chicken broth cube\n
3 cups water\n
1/2 teaspoon cumin\n
1/2 teaspoon black pepper\n
2 tbsp acid juice\n
Onion Seed\n
2 cloves of garlic\n
2 tbsp olive oil

    </string>
    <string name="sbanlsan5way">
        1. In a pot on the fire Put the oil, then add the chopped onions, garlic, pasta and stir flavored.\n
2. Add the spinach to them, add the lemon juice, the chicken broth cube, and 3 cups of water with black pepper and cumin.\n
3. Leave the pot on fire until the pasta is ripe and then serv
    </string>
    <string name="ryhansoupsauidainteg">
        1 and 1/2 kg basil, clip\n
6 cup chicken broth, equivalent to 6 cube broth dissolved in 6 cups water\n
2 tablespoons tomato paste\n
1/2 cup lemon juice lemon\n
2 tbsp butter\n
Black pepper sprinkle\n
Salt to taste
    </string>
    <string name="ryhansoupsaudiway">
        Put the butter in a pan and add to the basil and saute for 5 to 6 minutes.\n
2. Place the fried basil in a saucepan, add chicken broth and mix well, add tomato paste and lemon juice, and mix\n
Soup with salt and black pepper.\n
3 - Put the pot on a strong fire and leave until boiling, then reduce the fire and leave the basil soup to boil for about 15 to 20 minutes
Until the basil is cooked.
    </string>
    <string name="adaspototosoupinteg">
        3 tablespoons olive oil\n
2 chopped onion\n
1 cup red lentils\n
1 cup wheat\n
1 chopped potato\n
1 carrot cut\n
2 garlic cloves\n
3 cup chicken broth\n
1 tablespoon salt\n
1 tablespoon cumin\n
1 teaspoon pepper

    </string>
    <string name="adspototosoupway">
        1 - Fry onion and garlic in oil until yellowing color.\n
2. Add the carrots, potatoes, lentils and set them on fire until the ingredients are cooked.\n
3 - Add the wheat, salt, pepper and cumin and let them on the fire a little.\n
4 - Mix the electric bat and then raise the fire to heat and then feet.
    </string>
    <string name="Shawarmabreadinteg">
        1/2 kilo flour
5 tbsp powdered milk
35 g sugar
Tablespoon yeast
Teaspoon baking powder
1/4 cup vegetable oil
   Water cup 3/4
Salt spray

    </string>
    <string name="shawrmabreadway">
        1. Mix all ingredients together - except flour - well until smooth.\n
2. Add the flour and stir them until you have a suitable dough.\n
3. Leave the dough half an hour to rest.\n
4. Cut the dough and spit it out as shown in the video.\n
5. Lift the dough on the fire until it blinks from both sides.
    </string>
    <string name="KuftaHalabiinteg">
        Kilo and a half minced meat\n
50 g pine\n
125 g onions\n
parsley\n
3 pieces of pepper colors\n
25 g pepper\n
25 g salt\n
25 g Bharat\n
50 g olive oil
    </string>
    <string name="kuftahalabiway">
        1 - Peel onion and wash parsley and pepper colors and cut them.\n
2. Bake minced meat and toss it again with vegetables and add salt, spices and pepper.\n
3 - Shape the flesh fingers and add pine when forming.\n
4 - Add a Chinese oil and put the fingers of kofta.\n
5. Place in oven at 180 ° C until cooked or cooked in skewers as desired.\n
6. Place it on the serving plate.
    </string>
    <string name="perfectmkdosinteg">
        Kilo and a half eggplant small size\n
Kilo Flaville minced minced beef\n
100 g chopped nuts\n
3 tsp minced garlic\n
6 teaspoon salt\n
Quantity of olive oil
    </string>
    <string name="perfectmkdosway">
        Wash the eggplant and cut off the leg, and raise it in a large amount of water.\n
Place a lid smaller than the same pot over the eggplant so that it does not float.\n
Leave for 15 minutes until it wilts.\n
Remove it from the water and place it in the iced water, then completely clean it from the water.\n
Sprinkle the eggplant with salt and make in each unit a longitudinal section with the knife, put salt in it as well.\n
Place the eggplant in a strainer and feed for 3 hours.\n
Mix finely chopped garlic with walnuts, walnuts and a teaspoon of salt, and stir well.\n
Stuff eggplant with about 1 tablespoon.\n
Place the stuffed eggplant in the jars (cans or packagings), then fill the oil with the oil and leave it for two or three days.\n
Feet with different dishes.
    </string>
    <string name="Burnfingerinteg">
        Kilo lentils\n
400 g pasta\n
2 tablespoons minced garlic\n
Half a cup of pomegranate molasses\n
One quarter cup of sour juice\n
2 tablespoons salt\n
5 tablespoons of starch mixed with a quarter cup of water\n\n
Ornamental components:
5 cups vegetable oil\n
Three loaves of Arabic bread\n
3 pieces of fried onions\n
A cup of flour\n
Bouquet of Coriander\n
Tablespoon minced garlic\n
Two tablespoons of olive oil
    </string>
    <string name="burnfingerway">
        1. Cook the lentils until they are cooked for 30 minutes\n
.
2. Add the pasta to the lentils before it is cooked in 8 minutes\n
.
3. When the pasta is cooked, add chopped garlic, pomegranate syrup, sour juice and salt\n
.
4. Mix the starch with water and add to the lentil mixture until it becomes a cohesive mixture\n
.
Leave the mixture for 1 hour to cool down and then refrigerate for 3 hours\n
.
6. Heat the vegetable oil. In the meantime, cut the Arab bread into medium sized squares\n
.
7. Fry the bread with oil until it turns golden and set it aside\n
.
8. Cut the onions into the sides and add flour to the flour, and then sauté the onion with the oil until it becomes golden.\n
.
10. Fry the coriander and wash with water\n
.
11. In a small frying pan, add the olive oil with the chopped coriander and garlic and the heart until the coriander has withered\n
.

12. To decorate his finger, pour the mixture into a deep tray\n
.
13. Zinni burn his finger by placing the fried bread on the face, then add the onion on top of it, then coriander and garlic
.
    </string>
    <string name="mainchickenshawrmainteg">
        Kilo and a half chicken, sliced thin\n
2 tbsp lemon juice\n
A teaspoon of orange skin\n
A teaspoon of lemon flesh\n
Teaspoon vinegar\n
Teaspoon salt\n
2 teaspoons black pepper\n
Spoon chicken spice\n
Half teaspoon turmeric\n
Half teaspoon ground cloves\n
Half a teaspoon of crushed hill\n
Half teaspoon paprika\n
Half teaspoon chutney\n
Half teaspoon grated ginger\n
2 tbsp vegetable oil\n
3 onion slices thin slices\n
3 tomatoes
    </string>
    <string name="mainchickenshawrmamainway">
        Place chicken slices in a bowl with all spices, salt, pepper, lemon juice, vinegar, orange and lemon skin.\n
Take a good heart and cover the bowl and let them refrigerate for 4 hours.\n
Remove the tomato and leave it aside.\n
Put the oil in a large skillet over medium heat, add the chicken mixture on top of it and my heart until the color of the chicken changes.\n
Add onions and my heart for 5 minutes.\n
Add the Lord of the tomato and my heart, and leave it until the chicken is cooked.\n
You can add red pepper, pickled cucumbers or French fries to the shawarma.\n
They can also be served in sandwiches or in dishes alongside green salad and sesame salad.
    </string>
    <string name="egablbnainteg">
        4 tbsp brick\n
6 eggs\n
1/2 teaspoon baking powder (Baiking Powder)\n
Spray of spices\n
Salt spray\n
Tablespoon vegetable oil
    </string>
    <string name="egablbnaway">
        1. In a deep dish place the eggs.\n
2. Add salt, berry and baking powder.\n
3. Pour all the ingredients together with the handbrake well until the consistency is complete.\n
4. Put a pan over the fire and heat the vegetable oil.\n
5. Add the egg mixture and, after it is cooked from the bottom, turn it over to ripen on the other side.\n
6. Lift the eggs after maturity and place it on the dish.\n
7. Remove the cheese and then stir in the form of cylindrical sandwiches and sliced slices.

    </string>
    <string name="seneadgaginteg">
        Chicken chopped 8 parts\n
5 potatoes cut into medium sized cubes\n
1/2 cup olive oil\n
Cinnamon sticks\n
Spices\n
salt\n
black pepper\n
4 Laura Paper\n
1 tablespoon ground coriander crushed\n
2 tbsp garlic slices
    </string>
    <string name="seneadgagway">
        In a deep pot on the fire, roast the chicken with water, laurel,\n
        cinnamon and a small amount of salt
In the process, stir the potatoes in hot oil and then remove them from the oil\n
After boiling the chicken, lift it off the fire and leave it aside
In another deep bowl, broil the chicken with a portion of garlic, coriander, pepper and spices,\n
        and each amount of olive oil. Mix well to combine the chicken with the sauce.\n
Oven fever
Bring a tray and tray with aluminum foil
Fry the fried potatoes and sprinkle with the remaining amount of salt, garlic, pepper, coriander \n
        and spices
Chinese chicken cutters and Chinese aluminum foil
Pour the oven into the oven until it is fully ripe or for about one hour
    </string>
    <string name="taboulakenonasaladinteg">
        Parsley Bouquet\n
1 tomato\n
1/2 onion\n
1/2 cup mint\n
1/4 cup kenoa\n
Tablespoon lemon juice\n
Tablespoon olive oil\n
Black spices\n
Salt spray
    </string>
    <string name="taboulakenonasaldway">
        1. In a dish, place all ingredients, except lettuce.\n
2. Flipping well\n
3. In the serving dish, place the lettuce\n
4. Put the salad on the lettuce and be ready to serve.
    </string>
    <string name="tmatmbzetinteg">
        Tablespoon apple cider vinegar\n
Tablespoon olive oil\n
1/2 teaspoon thick\n
1/2 teaspoon garlic powder\n
Salt spray\n
Pack of watercress\n
1 cup chopped cherry tomatoes\n
1/4 cup black olives section
    </string>
    <string name="tmatmzetway">
        1. In a dish, place apple cider vinegar, olive oil, garlic, garlic powder and salt with stirring.\n
2. In the serving bowl, place the watercress.\n
3. Give the cherry tomatoes, then the olives.\n
4. On the face and the mix of the mixture you attended.
    </string>
    <string name="kratelbnanteg">
        100 g of goat cheese\n
2 tbsp thyme\n
2 tablespoons thick\n
2 tbsp lemon lemon juice\n
One teaspoon mustard\n
1 teaspoon olive oil\n
French lettuce\n
1/4 cup pomley\n
Cherry tomatoes
    </string>
    <string name="kratelbnaway">
        1. Shape the brick shaped balls.\n
2. Repeat it with every quantity you have.\n
3. Bake half the balls with the thyme, and the second half with the sumac.\n
4. In a dish place olive oil, lemon juice, mustard, mixed with.\n
5. In the serving dish and lettuce.\n
6. Place the white cheese balls with the pomelo and cherry tomatoes.\n
7. Mix them with lemon juice and olive oil and the salad is ready to serve.
    </string>
    <string name="foulb2donsinteg">
        1 packet of beans\n
1 piece of chopped tomatoes\n
1 small onion, chopped\n
3 tbsp chopped parsley\n
4 tbsp olive oil\n
salt\n
4 tbsp lemon juice
    </string>
    <string name="foulb2donsway">
        Mix the ingredients and olive oil on the face.
    </string>
    <string name="btatazbadyinteg">
        A potato\n
A tomato\n
Clove garlic\n
Vegetable oil for frying\n
1/2 onion\n
1 cup yogurt\n
1/2 teaspoon dry mint\n
2 tablespoons parsley\n
Tablespoon tomato paste\n
Black spices\n
Salt, to taste
    </string>
    <string name="btatazbadyway">
        1. In a pan on the fire, heat the vegetable oil.\n
2. Fry the potatoes with oil.\n
3. In another pan, heat new oil.\n
4. Put the onions and tomatoes and stir until they melt.\n
5. Add the tomato paste, stirring.\n
6. Pour them with salt and black pepper.\n
7. In a bowl of yogurt, add garlic, mint and salt and stir.\n
8. Place the potatoes in the serving bowl.\n
9. Fry them a mixture of tomatoes and onions.\n
10. On the face put a mixture of yogurt.\n
11. Garnish face with parsley and then feet.
    </string>
    <string name="shamndrlbnasaladinteg">
        500 g shelled peeled and cut\n
Salt spray\n
1/2 cup skimmed brick\n
3 teaspoons low fat mayonnaise\n
Clove garlic\n
3 tablespoons nut
    </string>
    <string name="shamndrlbnsaladaway">
        1. In a dish, place all the ingredients in the clear order of the video.\n
2. Make stirring until full homogeneity.\n
3. Pick up the power for the serving dish.
    </string>
    <string name="btatalbnasaladinteg">
        A boiled potato\n
2 tablespoons low-fat brick\n
2 tbsp hazelnut\n
Oregano workshop
    </string>
    <string name="btatalbnasaladway">
        1. Shape boiled sweet potatoes as it is clearly in front of you and put the dish.\n
2. On the face Put the low-fat brick as video.\n
3. Put the oregano and hazelnuts on the face and be ready to serve.
    </string>
    <string name="ssoneinteg">
       1 kg beetroot\n
1 onion\n
2 cloves of garlic\n
1 liter chicken broth (or vegetable broth)\n
2 Laurel paper\n
salt\n
pepper\n
To cut bread with garlic and chickpeas:\n
1 pack of chickpeas\n
1/2 teaspoon garlic powder\n
2 tbsp olive oil\n
For hot radish yogurt:\n
150 ml Greek yogurt\n
3 tbsp grated radish, sour cream or soft cream (or depending on the temperature of the favorite taste)\n
Salt according to taste
    </string>
    <string name="ssoneway">
        Heat the oven to 200 ° C.
2. Pepper and berry beet, ground onion and garlic. Leave it aside.\n
3.Place the chickpea and leave it until it dries.\n
4. Place the chickpea in a bowl and sprinkle with olive oil.\n
5. Add the garlic and salt powder. Mix the ingredients so that the chickpeas are covered with olive oil and garlic powder.\n
6. Place the chickpeas on an oven tray and bake for 20-25 minutes, stirring the chickpeas once or twice while baking.\n
7. During this time, prepare the Beet Soup.\n
8. Bake the garlic and onion in a little olive oil for a minute or until the mixture becomes soft, aromatic and disappears.\n
9. Add the beetroot and yeast for 5 minutes or until maturity.\n
10. Add the broth and laurel leaves. Cook the mixture over low heat for 15 minutes, or until the grated beet is cooked.\n
11. Once the beets are tender, mix the soup until the textures are softened with the manual beaker or roll into the blender until it becomes smooth.\n
12. Bring the soup with cream of radish, garlic-roasted chickpeas and zina with fresh thyme.\n
13.Bread radish: mix yogurt with radish in a bowl, add salt and mix well.

    </string>
    <string name="sstwointeg">
        3 cup cauliflower clip\n
1 cup crushed almonds\n
1 tbsp chopped celery\n
2 onion chopped\n
1 piece of butter\n
2 tablespoons flour\n
2 cube chicken broth\n
1 teaspoon salt\n
1 teaspoon pepper\n
1 teaspoon spices\n
1 teaspoon nutmeg\n
1 cup milk\n
1 cup chicken broth\n
3 parsley leaves for decoration
    </string>
    <string name="sstwoway">
        Cut cauliflower into small flowers without necks.\n
Bring a cooker and place cauliflower with celery and chopped onion. Add the chicken broth cup and set it on fire for 15 minutes.\n
Bake it slightly with food, then bring a pan and butter, then place the flour on it.\n
Add the soups and milk while stirring.\n
Add the chicken cubes, salt, spices, pepper and nutmeg and leave on fire for 10 minutes. Add the crushed almonds.\n
Sprinkle them in the serving dish and sprinkle with parsley leaves and then feet.
    </string>
    <string name="ssthreeinteg">
        Onion Seed\n
Clove garlic\n
Cup of Islands\n
A potato\n
A teaspoon of basil\n
3 cups chicken broth\n
Vegetable oil\n
2 tablespoons flour\n
3/4 cup of cooking cream\n
1/2 teaspoon salt\n
1/2 teaspoon black condiment\n
1/21 cup water

    </string>
    <string name="ssthreeway">
        1. In a pot on the fire, heat the oil.\n
2. Add the onions and stir.\n
3. Add the garlic and stir by stirring.\n
4. Then add carrots, potatoes with stirring.\n
5. Place the broth, the broth, and leave the pot on the fire until full maturity.\n
6. Meanwhile in a pan on the fire, heat the oil.\n
7. Add the flour and stir well.\n
8. Add the cooking cream, stirring.\n
9. Add water and stir.\n
10. Add the previous mixture pot of soup to the fire and stir by stirring.\n
11. Season with salt and black pepper.
    </string>
    <string name="ssfourinteg">
        1 kg milk\n
1 egg\n
1 tbsp starch powder\n
1 teaspoon salt
    </string>
    <string name="ssfourway">
        1 - Add the egg and starch to the milk and mix the mixture with the spoon well.\n
2. Place a strainer on a saucepan, rub the mixture over it and stir with the spoon until the milk mixture is completely filtered from the cream and any lumps.\n
3 - Put the amount of milk filtered on medium heat, paying attention to the continuous stirring so as not to overdo milk.\n
4. When the milk begins to boil, add the salt and stir for a minute and then remove the pot from the fire. So you have got cooked milk.
    </string>
    <string name="ssfiveinteg">
        1/2 cup of Spaghetti Spaghetti\n
2 tbsp vegetable oil\n
1 onion\n
4 Mushroom\n
1/2 cup gracious cooking\n
Salt spray\n
1/2 teaspoon oregano\n
1/2 teaspoon black pepper\n
1/2 teaspoon cumin\n
Cube meat broth\n
4 cups water
    </string>
    <string name="ssfiveway">
        1. Cut the mushrooms and onions.\n
2. Heat the oil in a pot on the fire.\n
3. Add the onion and stir with stirring, add the mushrooms and continue stirring.\n
4. After the onions and mushrooms fade, add the tongue of the sparrow and slightly brown.\n
5. Add a cube of meat broth, water, spices, and salt.\n
6. After maturation of the tongue of the bird add the cooking cream.\n
7. Leave the pot on the fire for 5 minutes and then be ready to serve.
    </string>
    <string name="sssixinteg">
        Cup of pasta\n
1 zucchini\n
1 Islands\n
1 onion\n
2 tomatoes\n
2 cloves of garlic\n
50 g coiled\n
1/2 cup mozzarella cheese\n
2 tbsp olive oil\n
1/2 teaspoon black pepper\n
Chicken broth cube\n
Chicken broth cup
    </string>
    <string name="sssixway">
        1. Cut onions, carrots, zucchini, tomatoes, and cabbage.\n
2. In a bowl, put the oil, add the onion and stir, then add the garlic.\n
3. After it is wet, add zucchini and carrots and continue stirring.\n
4. Add the tomatoes and wait for them to wither.\n
5. Add chicken broth, chicken broth cube, cabbage, pasta and wait until cooked.\n
6. After ripening and boiling add the red beans and black pepper and then leave the pot on the fire for an additional 5 minutes.\n
7. Add the cheese and the soup is ready to serve.
    </string>
    <string name="ssseveninteg">
        1/2 cup chopped parsley\n
1/2 kg of tomatoes\n
2 tbsp minced mint\n
3 tbsp hot red pepper paste\n
1 medium onion cut into 4 parts\n
6 tbsp lemon juice fresh acid\n
4 tbsp olive oil\n
Salt Brush\n
Trout Spices and Halabi Pepper\n
1/2 cups coarse broccoli\n
For decoration:\n
Clip option\n
Pepper\n
Minced mint and parsley

    </string>
    <string name="sssevenway">
        1 - Peel tomatoes and cut into quarters; peel onion and cut into quarters.\n
2. Fry parsley and mint. Fry the pepper and cucumber, freshly sour.\n
3 - Boil some water and leave the burghul for 10 minutes, until it becomes soft. Lay it out.\n
4. Put all ingredients in a mixer, tomatoes, onions, water, pepper paste, seasoning, acid juice;\n
5 - pour in a bowl, add the bulgur and taste the dish, to modify the spices. Garnish with chopped cucumber and chopped peppers.\n
6. Give it cold.
    </string>
    <string name="sdoneinteg">
        1 kg liquid milk\n
1 cup small starch dissolved in a small glass of water\n
5 tablespoons sugar\n
1/2 teaspoon water of dice\n
fruits :\n
1 cup mango juice\n
        1 teaspoon starch\n
1 tablespoon sugar

    </string>
    <string name="sdoneway">
        Dilute the starch, then season and pour over the cold milk, add the sugar and put the milk on the fire with stirring constantly until boiling.\n
Leave the milk boiling for 5 minutes then add the water and cast the fire.\n
Sprinkle the mixture in cups or yogurt and leave to cool and freeze.\n
To prepare the mango layer, diced the starch, and then mix it with the juice.\n
        Put it on the fire to boil with the stirring constantly, pour it over the mixture in a thin layer and let it cool.
    </string>
    <string name="sdtwointeg">
        5 cup flour\n
2 cups sugar\n
3 eggs\n
Salt spray\n
1 tablespoon vanilla\n
1 cup of margarine\n
Lemon lemons\n
1 tablespoon Baiking Powder\n
2 tablespoons grated coconut\n
For decoration of liquid chocolate, Jam, Nuts

    </string>
    <string name="sdtwoway">
        Bring a bowl and whisk the eggs with sugar and vanilla well then add the ghee and dip again.\n
Add flour, salted broth, lemon juice, coconut and baking powder and mix well.\n
Shake the dough on a smooth surface sprinkled with flour as desired, then place the shapes in a baking tray coated with butter.\n
Pour the chicken into the oven until the petivore is cooked and then add it with jam or chocolate and nuts and then feet.\n
    </string>
    <string name="sdthreeinteg">
        2 cups oval paste
2 cups water
3/4 cup condensed condensed milk
1/4 cup corn starch
1/4 cup diameter
1/4 cup pistachios
Vegetable oil sprayer
    </string>
    <string name="sdthreeway">
        1. Cupcake molds with vegetable oil.\n
2. Place the dough with the molds.\n
3. On the face spray the oil again.\n
4. Enter the Chinese oven for 20 minutes.\n
5. In a pot on the fire put water, condensed milk, corn starch and stirring until you get the appropriate texture.\n
6. Anchor the kanafa with the diameter.\n
7. Remove the kanafa from the molds and place it in the serving bowl.\n
8. Put the condensed milk mixture on the face.\n
9. Garnish face with pistachio
    </string>
    <string name="sdfourinteg">
        2 egg white\n
Colorful food\n
Teaspoon lemon lemon juice\n
1/2 cup ground almonds\n
1 cup sugar powder\n
1/2 cup cream blended\n
Two strawberries

    </string>
    <string name="sdfourway">
        1. In a bowl place the egg white, then hit with the electric bat until it gets creamy.\n
2. Add the colored food and stir with stirring.\n
3. Add lemon juice and stir again.\n
4. Add crushed almonds, powdered sugar and stir-fry.\n
5. In a tray lined with butter, place the mixture in the form of circular units as shown in front of you.\n
6. Enter the Chinese oven for 20 minutes.\n
7. Bake the biscuit with cream and whisk it over the slices of strawberries then on the face Put another layer of biscuits.

    </string>
    <string name="sdfiveinteg">
        1 kg liquid milk\n
1 cup small starch dissolved in a small glass of water\n
5 tablespoons sugar\n
1/2 teaspoon water of dice\n
fruits :\n
1 cup pulp of Bashan\n
1 teaspoon starch\n
1 tablespoon sugar

    </string>
    <string name="sdfiveway">
        1 - Dilute the starch and then sauté and pour over the cold milk, add sugar and put the milk on the fire with stirring even permanent

Boiling.\n

Leave the milk boiling for 5 minutes then add the water and cast the fire from the fire.\n

3 - Pour the mixture in cups or yogurt and leave it to the bird and freeze.\n

4 - To prepare the layer Bashan, dipped starch and sauce and then the line with the pulp Bashan, put it on the fire to boil with stirring permanently, spike

Click the mixture in a thin layer and let it cool down.

    </string>
    <string name="sdsixinteg">
        Sweet potato\n
Tablespoon sugar\n
1/2 1 tablespoon melted butter\n
2 tablespoons nut\n
Teaspoon cinnamon
    </string>
    <string name="sdsixway">
        1. In a tray lined with aluminum foil, place the potatoes.\n

2. Enter the Chinese oven for 40 minutes.\n

3. Divide the potatoes in half.\n

4. Fry them from the inside in a bowl.\n

5. Add the butter and cinnamon to the pulp of the potato and stir.\n

6. In a tray lined with butter paper put a mold, and in the mold put the potatoes.\n

7. Enter the Chinese oven for 5 minutes.\n

8. Meanwhile in the bowl mix the sugar with walnuts.\n

9. After the tray has been removed from the oven, replace the mold with the serving bowl\n

10. Put sugar and walnuts on the face.

    </string>
    <string name="sdseveninteg">
        2 cups rice\n
5 cups water\n
2 cups sugar\n
2 cups Akkawi cheese\n
1/4 cup water of roses\n
Satisfied\n
1 cup crushed pistachios

    </string>
    <string name="sdsevenway">
        1 - Wash the cheese well.\n
2 - Wash rice and soak in water for an hour and then put in a pressure suit and leave for 45 minutes and then brush him.\n
3. Add the sugar gradually and stir it, add the rose water and the mascara and my heart well.\n
4. Add the cheese gradually with the continuous stirring, then pour the mixture in serving dishes and sprinkle with crushed pistachios and hot feet.
    </string>
    <string name="essixinteg">
        1/2 cup white rice\n
2 chicken breast\n
1 small onion\n
1/4 cup oatmeal\n
5 cups water\n
Salt and black pepper to taste\n
3 Clove Love\n
1 lemon citric acid
    </string>
    <string name="essixway">
        1 - Cut the chicken breast into small cubes, put it in a pot of fire with two cups of water and when boiling, add the beads of cloves
And let him boil a little.\n
2. When the chicken is cooked, cut the onion and add it with the chicken, add the salt as desired.\n
3 - Wash and spread rice for 5 minutes and then add to the chicken with the rest of the water, cover the pot until it is cooked and after 10 minutes I lay
Fire, and mix it with the handbrake quickly until all the ingredients are homogenized.\n
4 - restore the pot on fire, if thick or thick mixture you can add water to ease it then add oats, parsley and lemon and the rest
Ingredients and leave on fire until cooked.
    </string>
    <string name="edfourinteg">
        A packet of cream. A cup of vegetable oil.\n
Two eggs. Cup of semolina.\n
        Cup of grated coconut. \n
        A cup of white sugar.\n
        A teaspoon of liquid flannel.\n
        A tablespoon of Nescafe powder.\n
        Two tablespoons of baking powder .\n
        Sixteen tablets of Oreo, cut into small pieces.\n
        Qatar, (Sharbat or Shire).
    </string>
    <string name="edfourway">
        Place the blender in the mixer, and place in each of the following:\n
        oil, egg, and cream, and then set the blender mixture, and cook it at medium speed until the ingredients are mixed together. \n
        Then add the semolina, vanilla, coconut, white sugar, And mix them all for a few seconds, and finally add both Benderj Bador and a spoon of Nescafe, then my heart all the ingredients together.\n
        Add a few pieces of small Oreo biscuits to the mixture and the ingredients of the ingredients together using a wooden spoon.\n
        Bring a medium sized tray, add it with vegetable oil or butter as you can, and mix it.\n
        Pour the porridge into the oven after you have heated it at an average temperature of 180 degrees Celsius, if the oven is cooked in a centimeter, or if it is Fahrenheit, heat it at three hundred and fifty degrees Fahrenheit for half an hour, then heat The top of the oven for five minutes, and then five minutes from the bottom of the oven.\n
        After the maturation of the pesosia, remove them from the oven, pour the dice on it, and let them drink for five minutes.\n
        During this time, the remaining pieces of oreo, then the sliced ​​biscuits on the face of the bispousa, were thrown.\n
        Cut the peas into equal sized squares and then let them in the fridge for at least 60 minutes.\n
        Remove them after a while and place them on the serving dish, and cool them with whatever you want from your family.
    </string>


    <string name="gdoneinte">
        1/21 cup crushed dates\n
1/4 cup butter or margarine\n
1 tablespoon water and rose\n
Paste Pastry Paste\n
Ground nuts\n
Pistachio Pistachios\n
scrambled eggs\n
sesame
    </string>
    <string name="gdoneway">
        1. In a bowl, place the crushed dates, butter and rose water, then stir until the mixture is completely blended.\n
2. On the baking paste, separate the past paste as shown before you.\n
3. Place crushed nuts and crushed pistachios on the face.\n
4. Fold the dough into cylindrical shape as video.\n
5. Cut the dough into circles as it is clearly in front of you.\n
6. Put the jewelry in a tray lined with butter paper.\n
7. Heat the face with whipped eggs and then add the sesame seeds.\n
8. Enter the Chinese oven at 180 degrees for 15 minutes.
    </string>
    <string name="gdtwointeg">
        Half a kilo of cocoa powder Gentlemen.\n
        Cup of milk powder. 150 grams of melted butter.\n
        Cup of fine sugar. Half cup of water.\n
        If we want to prepare shakula fat we increase the amount of butter 250 g.\n
        As for the preparation of chocolate pills remain the ingredients as they are and add the nuts as desired and here we will use whole grains of nuts and almonds.\n
        Aluminum foil clip small boxes.


    </string>
    <string name="gdtwoway">
        We add the powdered milk and the water and leave it with the water bath with continuous stirring, adding cocoa powder and sugar and stirring the mixture until we have a thick homogeneous mixture, can increase water as needed, provided that the density is not less, And are formed and poured easily.\n
        A small amount of water is added from time to time until we have a homogeneous mixture of chocolate. \n
        Leave to cool slightly with stirring from time to time. We prepare aluminum foil and then pour a small amount of chocolate with a piece of hazelnut or almonds and then close the aluminum sheet, chocolate is formed as desired, where you can prepare in a circular or rectangular or square, with the possibility of using small silicone molds for chocolate, Remove the chocolate from the mold after it has frozen and bonded and wrapped with aluminum foil as desired.\n
        We bring the whole amount of the then then we put it in the refrigerator for two hours until they hold together well then they are taken cold.

    </string>
    <string name="gdthreeinteg">
        2 cups flour\n
11/2 cup soft semolina\n
1/2 cup of fresh milk\n
200 grams butter\n
1\4 cup tahini\n
2 tbsp turmeric\n
3 tbsp baiking powder\n
1 cup of sugar\n
1/2 cup of fresh milk\n
3 \ 4 1 cup water
    </string>
    <string name="gdthreeway">
        1. Mix dry ingredients together with flipping.\n
2. Add the butter and tahini and mix well.\n
3. Add the water and mix well until the mixture becomes soft.\n
4. Grease a tray with the tahini and pour the mixture\n
5. Brush the pine nuts on the surface.\n
6. Bake in a protective oven for 45 minutes.\n
7. Then rise from the oven and leave to cool completely and then cut.

    </string>
    <string name="gdfourinteg">
        11 \ 2 microbial\n
1/4 cup oil\n
1 tablespoon honey\n
Salt spray\n
1/4 cup crushed nuts\n
1 cup apricot jam\n
1 cup cashew nuts
    </string>
    <string name="gdfourway">
        Bring the bowl and mix the flour with oil, nuts, salt and honey well.\n
Bring the tart cakes and put the paste and press on them and then stick them with a fork so as not to bulge.\n
Insert the oven molds until they are ripe.\n
Bring it to the jam and sprinkle with the cashew nuts and then put it on your fee
    </string>
    <string name="gdfiveinteg">
        1 cup semolina\n
1 cup powdered milk\n
1 cup soft sugar\n
3 tablespoons cream\n
1 cup nuts\n
1 cup dried fruits
    </string>
    <string name="gdfiveway">
        In a pot of fire, put the semolina, powdered milk and my heart until it turns yellow. Add sugar, dried fruit, cream and my heart well.\n
Pour the mixture into the cupcake molds and place them in the freezer until they are firm and then remove them with cupcakes and nuts.
    </string>
    <string name="gdsixinteg">
        A cup of butter\n
Cup of condensed milk and local\n
3/4 cup brown sugar\n
1 teaspoon liquid vanilla\n
2 cups flour\n
1/2 cup peanut butter\n
1/2 cup chocolate granules
    </string>
    <string name="gdsixway">
        1. In the blender, put butter, condensed condensed milk, brown sugar, and peanut butter.\n
2. Mix and add the liquid vanilla and continue mixing until you get the right consistency.\n
3. Add the flour with mixing until the homogenization is complete.\n
4. Add a portion of the chocolate granules to the dough that you have mixed with the mixture and then place them in a tray lined with butter paper.\n
5. On the fire in a water bath, put the chocolate beans with the pistachio butter and stir until the mixture is fully dissolved.\n
6. Mix the mixture in Chinese and face on the face.\n
7. Enter the Chinese refrigerator until it is cool and firm.\n
8. Then cut it and its feet.
    </string>
    <string name="gdseveninteg">
        1 cup flour\n
3 tablespoons butter\n
1 cup liquid cheese\n
1 cup strawberry jam
    </string>
    <string name="gdsevenway">
        Mix flour, butter and cheese well.\n
Remove the paste with a pinch on the surface of the touch, sprinkled with flour.\n
Cut the dough in a circular cut.\n
Place the dough in the cake molds and bake in the oven until it is cooked for 30 minutes.\n
Stuff the mini tart with the strawberry jam and then her feet.
    </string>


    <string name="maind">Main Dishes
    </string>


    <string name="saladd">Salad</string>

    <string name="soupd">Soup</string>
    <string name="dessert">Dessert</string>


</resources>
